const questions = {
  'How many technologies do you use?': {
    question: `How many technologies do you use?`,
    answer: `We offer 3D printing and Additive Manufacturing solutions for eight technologies:-
    <ol type="i"><li><strong>FDM/FFF</strong> fused filament fabrication printing</li><li><strong>DLP</strong> digital light projection</li><li><strong>MJP</strong> multi jet printing</li><li><strong>CJP</strong> colour jet printing</li><li><strong>SLA</strong> stereo- lithography apparatus</li><li><strong>SLS</strong> selective laser sintering</li><li><strong>DMP</strong> direct metal printing</li><li><strong>GDP</strong> gel dispensing printing</li></ol>`
  },
  'How long will my part take to 3D print?': {
    question: `How long will my part take to 3D print?`,
    answer: `Small plastic parts typically take 1-2 days, medium parts 2-3 days, and large parts 3-5 days. For SLA, it is typically 5-7 days and for DMP it is 10-15 days.`
  },
  'Can you print batches or parts?': {
    question: `Can you print batches or parts?`,
    answer: `Batch production is offered. Depending on the quantities, we may propose a different technology or material to that requests.`
  },
  'What colour will my part be?': {
    question: `What colour will my part be?`,
    answer: `We will use the materials loaded in the machine to reduce lead time. Swapping to special materials is possible but a material changeover fee may be required. For FDM | FFF printing, there is a larger choice of materials and colours. So please request your preferred colour. For full colour parts we use the CJP technology.`
  },
  'Can clear parts be printed?': {
    question: `Can clear parts be printed?`,
    answer: `Clear parts are offered via the MJP and SLA technologies. How clear the parts is depends on the geometry and materials used. In some cases the part may be more translucent than clear.`
  },
  'Do you offer high temperature materials?': {
    question: `Do you offer high temperature materials?`,
    answer: `We offer high temp materials such as PEI / Ultem, PPSU, PEKK, PEEK and ThermecZED.`
  },
  'Will my part be post processed?': {
    question: `Will my part be post processed?`,
    answer: `Supports are removed as standard, unless otherwise specified. Other post processing techniques are offered, but at a price.`
  },
  'How accurate will my part be?': {
    question: `How accurate will my part be?`,
    answer: `The part accuracy will be as good as the technology will allow. Part orientation can affect part accuracy, which we sometimes cannot change. The part will be inspection to ensure it meets the required quality threshold.`
  },
  'What is the largest part that can be produced?': {
    question: `What is the largest part that can be produced?`,
    answer: `1800mm x 1450mm x 1100mm.`
  },
  'What is the layer thickness that can be printed?': {
    question: `What is the layer thickness that can be printed?`,
    answer: `From 10 microns min using DLP; up to 1.3mm max. using GDP.`
  },
  'Do you offer an end-to-end managed service?': {
    question: `Do you offer an end-to-end managed service?`,
    answer: `For a fully managed project (inc. design, engineering, scanning, printing, post processing - all to customer specification - we recommend CDG.<br /><br />Tel. +44 1420 88645.<br />Email <a href="mailto:info@cdg.uk.com">info@cdg.uk.com</a>.`
  },
};

export default questions;